(THIS IS A SEMI-BETA BUILD OF EEEHUD, UNLISTED RELEASE)
screenshot and report any fucked up things you see that i can fix, this hud was created solely for myself but maybe with testing it could become public and stable, ready to be put on huds.tf
send any bugged things to me through the discussions on the steam group: http://steamcommunity.com/groups/EEEHUD and don't forget to tell me your settings. (resolution, customizations, ratio)

happy testing idots :^)

Full Release Checklist: (✔ = Functional, X = Not Working, ? = Untested, * = Unneccessary for release, ! = Bugged/Unfinished see known problems)

Runs on:
Windows = ✔
Mac* = X
Linux* = X
16:9 = ✔
16:10* = ?
4:3* = ?

Can play these gamemodes:
Tournament = ✔
Casual = ✔
Competitive = ?
Mann Vs. Machine = ✔!
Payload = ✔
Payload Race = ✔	
Control Points = ✔
Attack/Defend = ✔
Capture the Flag = ✔
King of the Hill = ✔	
Domination = ✔
Special Delivery = ✔
Arena* = ✔
Player Destruction = ✔!
Mannpower = ✔
Territorial Control = ✔	
Passtime* = ✔!
Robot Destruction* = ✔!
Halloween = ✔

Currently known problems:
Using the 6s scoreboard in MvM is buggy, use normal for now.
MvM end game screen is using default hud.
The cosmetic (+) button screen is bugged, might be on valve's end though.
In Player Destruction, cannot see current amount of beers you are holding.
In Passtime, the ball location on the HUD is not visible.
Robot Destruction currently using default hud.